{
    "id": "ec040b090d6f4b38a84e1678e2b978d2",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns and Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jane is the woman …………. keeps giant lizards in the garden shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The person ……………… keeps giant lizards in the garden shed is Jane.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Giant lizards are ……………… Jane keeps in the garden shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. Jane keeps in the garden shed are giant lizards.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The garden shed is the place ……………. Jane keeps giant lizards.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The place ……………… Jane keeps giant lizards is the garden shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The secretary is …………….. Mark is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Tuesday was the day ……………….. I went to London to meet James.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The day ………………. I went to London to meet James was Tuesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "when",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "To meet James was the reason …………… I went to London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "why",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}